one, two, three, four, five...
GALLIGARI CHANNEL GO GO!
And so, today's project
Today's project is
I went to a stylish lunch
Stylish!
Roppongi, so this is the place to go.
This is...
I'm taking it back.
It's Roppongi, after all.
I'd like to go somewhere nice.
I'd like to go there.
Here's a video.
They are good friends.
Yes, so the food arrived, so here's what it looks like.
Pay together
Ooh!
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Where did you order it from?
Let's see...
Chicken with tomatoes.
What's this?
Kimua.
There's some kind of soy sauce on the bottom.
Soy Sauce Vegetables
I think it's grilled chicken.
What kind of dressing is this?
Did it say?Did it say?
No, it didn't say anything about the dressing.
But it was really good.
What kind of chicken?
It's a little refreshing.
Yeah, it's good, isn't it?
Yum.
It's fancy.
Have you ever had dinner in Roppongi?
Oh, I've had something like that once...
Yes, I have.
Are you with me?
Did you go to a burger place?
It's not a burger.
Once after work.
I think I went there once after work.
With someone?
Yeah.
Between jobs.
I think we went somewhere in the middle.
Not south?
Possible!
And it's Sunday.
Yes!
Ugh.
I get hearts here, you know.
I hate it.
It's so bad.
Ugh. I really, really can't.
I'm really sorry.I'm really sorry, but...
I really can't.
You know what it is?
This bread tastes like something.
It's sour.
What?
How do you do it?
Salad is delicious.
Oh, no...
You don't like it.
No, I'm not.
I can eat leafy greens like this.
What's so hard?
Well, cucumbers, for example.
Hmmm...
Tomatoes.
Heh.
Carrots?
No.
Radishes?
Stocks?
No.
Pakuchi?
Lettuce and cabbage are okay.
Yes, lettuce and cabbage.
It smells like curry.
Cane?
Frog. It's not a frog.Frogs, not frogs.
I'm scared! I'm so scared!
There's a very scary man here.
Curry?
Curry.
You don't often have dinner with Momoka, do you?
No, not as often as I'd like.
Just the two of you?
Oh, no, not always.
Right.
We used to go out a long time ago. A really long time ago.
Oh, Jonathan, isn't it?
What?
I've been there.
And we went to drink tapioca together.
Yes!
But it was just that one time.
Really?
Maybe that was the only time we met and hung out on a holiday.
Momoka suddenly invited me to a tapioca shop in Sangen-jaya.
That's a serious level, right?
Yeah, that's really about it.
Is there anything you haven't tried yet that you'd like to try?
Is there anything you'd like to try?
Oh, that one!
Nyokki
Jyokki.
Do you know it?
I know what it's called.
I don't know what it is.Because I'm wondering what it is.
I'm sure it's something to do with soybeans.
Yeah, it's a lot of things.
What would you like for your last supper?
Beef tongue.
I'm full.
I don't like it.
What do you want?
Peach ice cream.
Momo ice cream.
Is it dinner? I don't think so.
We'll have a family pack or something.
I see.
Until my stomach hurts too much to eat.
Today...
I'm filming for youtube.
This is the first one.
Momoka, what were you filming earlier?
Dance quiz
Oh, did you get it?
Yes, I did!
But you said it was hard.
But we did dance to "Okay, Magical.
Oh, my God.
Doesn't that make you nostalgic?
So Misaki guessed it?
Yeah, she did.
That's for sure.
I often have dinner at night.
Take a bath and go to bed.I'm going to take a bath and go to bed.
After dinner that night
I thought I'd open up a bit before I went to the bathroom.
Why?
I don't know. I just felt like it wouldn't be good to go in right away.
After dinner?
Yeah. - What?
What? Yeah?
What? That's what you said.
So I'm going back to my room.
And while I was waiting...
I'm having a hard time taking a bath.
Yes, I know.
Can't you just start the bath with a bang?
That's right.
That's why I have to take a break.
Then I can't get up.
I sleep till morning and wake up in the morning to take a bath.
Morning bath.
I want to fix that.
But I think a morning bath is more efficient for me.
Well...
It helps with swelling and wakes you up.
You often hear that a cold shower in the morning is good?
Oh, I see.
Swelling really does get worse with age.
Hmm?
What?
I never used to get swollen.
But even now, when I wake up in the morning, I feel it.Even now, when I wake up in the morning, I'm so swollen, I can feel it.
I think my eyes are swollen too.
And at the same time, my face is swollen all over.
I wonder why.
I don't know.
I think I took a lot off.
I took a lot of it off.
It looks like this.
I'll eat the rest on my own.
As you wish.
There's still some left for both of us.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye!
I'm home!
No, it was really good.
I didn't even change much.
I didn't change much, but I'm having a heartwarming meal.
I hope those who enjoy it are enjoying it
I hope you enjoyed it.
So, thank you very much for watching!
Thank you very much.
If you liked this video, please subscribe to our channel
If you liked this video, please subscribe to the channel, click the good button, and leave a comment!
Bye-bye!
Bye, bye, bye.